https://www.pgcf.ca/privacy-policy

Donate Now
How Do I Donate?
Every gift to the Prince George Community Foundation is important, regardless of size. Every gift helps enhance the services and opportunities in our community. The Foundation is grateful to receive continuing support from individuals, families, organizations, foundations, businesses and corporations.
The Prince George Community Foundation gratefully accepts the following types of gifts:
Cash, cheques, Visa, MasterCard, money orders
Multi-year pledges - in the form of post-dated cheques, automatic monthly/yearly Visa or MasterCard payments or through a payment schedule
Stocks and bonds
Real estate and other assets
Gifts made through estate planning, such as bequests, life insurance policies, charitable remainder trusts, annuities
We invite you to make a donation to The Prince George Community Foundation today!
Your friends, neighbours, business associates and acquaintances are involved and support the Prince George Community Foundation for many reasons. Some have contributed to the foundation to establish a named endowment to honour their family or business . . . and to show their commitment to our community.
Others have contributed to the Foundation in memory of a special person or event in their life. The donation and endowed fund in their name will act as a legacy of their contribution to our community.
We would be pleased to discuss various options with you regarding a contribution to the Foundation. Opportunities exist for you to designate your gifts to benefit specific projects, organizations or areas of the community for which you have particular interests.
Donate Now!
Privacy Policy
About Prince George Community Foundation
Prince George Community Foundation, established in 1995, works with individuals, corporations, and charitable agencies to create permanent endowment funds and then uses the income from those funds to support thousands of charities.
Every year, through the generous support of donors, Prince George Community Foundation funds hundreds of innovative projects in areas such as arts and culture, education, environment, sports & recreation, health, and social development.
Prince George Community Foundation brings together donors, non-profits, and charities, government, media, and academic institutions, local leaders, and passionate individuals to build meaningful and lasting change in northern BC.
Consent
By using the Prince George Community Foundation’s services, you consent to the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will not be collected or used for any other purpose without your consent. We will not actively collect personal information for the purpose of sale or marketing in a way that specifically identifies you. In other words, we don’t sell user data. Individuals may withdraw their consent at any time, by any means, with reasonable notice to the Prince George Community Foundation; however, consent cannot be withdrawn retroactively.
Types of Information Collected
Prince George Community Foundation does not collect information indiscriminately. The types of information collected are limited to only that which is necessary and reasonable to fulfill its purposes. The Prince George Community Foundation collects personal information by lawful means and noes not intentionally mislead individuals about the purposes for which information is being collected.
Some of the types and means by which personal information is collected by the Prince George Community Foundation include:
Information is collected automatically from the Prince George Community Foundation website, including:
the Internet Protocol Address and domain name used (the Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either to the donor’s Internet service provider or directly to the donor’s computer; this address can be translated to determine the domain name of the donor’s service provider, e.g. pgcf.ca);
the type of browser and operating system;
the date and time of the visit;
and the web pages or services accessed.
Prince George Community Foundation may collect and record personal information provided to us by an individual through correspondence, conversations, meetings, conferences, donations, or other forms of communication.
Information may be collected from public sources.
These types and means by which personal information is collected by the Prince George Community Foundation are not intended to be an exhaustive list, and the Prince George Community Foundation may collect personal information about an individual from time to time by other means as is consistent with its purposes.
Information Obtained Automatically – (Cookies)
The Prince George Community Foundation uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our websites. We, and our third-party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our websites. In certain circumstances, your implied consent to our accessing, using or disclosing may be provided if you do not instruct your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is sent or if you do not opt-out of other services.
A cookie is a small data file that websites commonly send to browsers. A cookie file contains information that can identify users. Cookies don't identify people personally, but rather identify an individual’s computer when they visit our site (which could potentially enable your identification). A cookie cannot read data off hard disks or read cookie files created by other sites. Prince George Community Foundation will not use this computer identification to further identify individual users. A browser can be set to warn the computer user before accepting cookies. In this case, the computer user will receive the warning message with each cookie. The computer user may choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in their browser; however, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of our services. If you do not instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, your consent to our use of the Personal Information may be implied.
Use of Personal Information
Collected personal information will only be used by authorized Prince George Community Foundation staff, to fulfill the purpose for which it was originally collected, for specific purposes if directed by the individual from whom the personal information is being collected, or for a use consistent with the original purpose. We may also use your personal information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our services, to provide the service on our behalf, to perform service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our service is used. Third parties are required to safeguard personal information entrusted to them in a manner consistent with the policies of the Prince George Community Foundation and are required to sign a confidentiality agreement as part of all contracts.
Personal Information Disclosures
Prince George Community Foundation treats personal information in our custody and/or control with the highest degree of confidentiality and only discloses it for the purpose for which it was collected, as required by law, or in specific circumstances with the consent of the relevant individual.
We have put in place contractual and other organizational safeguards with our staff to ensure a proper level of protection of your personal information.
Prince George Community Foundation does not sell, share or disclose your personal information to others for any type of mailing list. We will not disclose or transfer your personal information to third parties without your permission, except as specified in this Privacy Policy.
Your personal information may be available to the Canadian government or its agencies under a lawful order, irrespective of the safeguards we have put in place for its protection.
Access to Information
You are entitled to access your personal information that the Prince George Community Foundation has in its custody and control. To request a copy of your personal information, please submit a request to the Prince George Community Foundation at the contact information provided below. We will respond to all requests for information within 30 days.
info@pgcf.ca7770 Brunswick StreetPrince George, BC, V2L 2C2(250) 562-7772
Copyright © 2015-2020 Prince George Community Foundation. All rights reserved.
